（古巴 哈瓦那）
我们换上的零件有福特 普利茅斯和凯迪拉克的
We swap in parts from Ford Plymouths and Cadillac.
我祖父1957年买下了它
My grandfather bought it in 1957.
他死后就传给了我爸 然后传给我哥 现在到我了
When he died it passed to my father, Then my brother and now to me.
看看这个 这是船上用的发动机
Look at this, this is an engine from a boat.
- 不会吧 - 没错！
- No way - Yeah!
只要能让它动起来就行
Whatever it takes to keep it running.
这正是古巴精神所在
This is a cuban spirit.
是你的精神所在吧 可别弄丢了
Your spirit, keep it up. Never ever lose that.
多姆
Dom.
你表弟他 他有麻烦了 快走！
It's your cousin. He's in trouble, come quickly!
快点 快点
Come on, come on.
别这样好吗 我知我有问题
Please don't do this, Understand my problem.
拿走这车我靠什么吃饭
You know I can't make living without my car.
别怪我 老兄
Isn't my problem bro.
多米尼克·托雷托 久仰大名啊
Dominic Toretto, I heard about you.
欢迎来到我的地盘
Welcome to my island.
干嘛扣我表弟的车？
Why he hooking up my cousin's car?
早前他跟我借钱 之后还不上 那我就把车拿走
In the morning, I gave it to him. He can't pay. I take the car.
再宽限我几天就行
I just need a few more days.
当初可没约好要宽限
Few more days isn't part of the deal.
得啦
Come on.
有了约定 就要说到做到
You make a deal you gotta live up to it.
既然有了约定！你做不到也得做到
You make a deal! You gonna live up to it.
做不到也得做到？
Gonna live up to it?
原来你玩的也是套路啊
So you are one of those types.
先搞到别人的车 再转运回美国对吧
You take everyone's ride and then ship it back to the states.
对自己人放尊重点儿
You should show your people some respect.
你说话给我小心点儿
You watch your mouth.
你这下出大事了
Now you got a problem.
我现在不谈人只谈车
I'm gonna keep it about the cars.
我真的被吓住了
I am really scared.
你想要车？得光明正大地要
You want a car? Get it the right way.
- 怎么着 - 飙一把试试
- How? - Race war.
车已经是我的了 老兄
I already own it, bro.
不是那辆车
Not that car.
赌我的
Mine.
多姆 他的车可是岛上最快的
Dom, his car is the fastest car in the Island.
知道他装了什么吗？
Do you know what he has under the hood?
知道他车里装什么并不重要？
Do you know, it doesn't matter what's under a hood?
真正重要的是谁来掌控方向盘
The only thing that matters is who's behind the wheel.
- 是吗？- 那还有假
- You think so? - I know so.
那就赌他的车
Then race his car.
我们不跑四分之一英里
We ain't racing a quarter mile here.
按古巴这里的长度来跑
We race the cuban mile.
就这样！
Done!
我很感激你挺身而出
I appreciate you what you're trying to do.
但我的车是岛上最慢的车
My car is the slowest car on the Island.
曾经是！
Was…
把座椅 车门 电源都拆掉
Pull the seats the doors the battery…
除了发动机之外 剩下的都不要
It ain't the motor, take it off.
- 一氧化亚氮吗？- 不 费南多 这是古巴版的氧化亚氮
- Laughing gas? - Nah, Fed. This is cuban NOS.
你们真是疯了
You guys are crazy.
- 你这是干什么 - 山寨版涡轮
- What are you doing? - Warm as turbo.
把真空管路拉起来接好！
Pull that back in line…Hold on!
都是老司机的老把戏
Old trick used to play.
以防万一
In case of emergencies.
你知道发动机承受不了那么大劲儿
You know that's way too much booze for that engine.
- 这不是要快嘛 - 可能会爆缸的
- It's going to be fast - It's gonna be a bomb.
跑完全程就够了
Only needs to go a mile.
我的家人 准备好了吗？
Are you ready for this, family?
这里是哈瓦那！
This is Havana!
开快点儿！
Be fast!
注意安全！
Be safe!
但别落后 车手准备好？
But don't be last. Racers ready?
走吧！
Go!
停
Stop.
老兄 那车就该呆在垃圾堆里
That car belongs in the trash bro.
- 停一下 - 停下
- Stop - Stop.
- 他们要去哪 - 谁知道 追上去
- Where are we going? - I don't know. Let's go.
- 偷袭他 - 好的
- Go steer - Si.
再见了 托雷托
Adios, Toretto.
好了 伙计 看看这个能不能行
Ok, buster… Let's see if this works.
这怎么可能啊
That's impossible…
小心
Look out.
说话就得算数
A deal's a deal.
你赢了我的车
You own my car.
也同样嬴取了我的尊重
And you earn my respect.
留着吧
Keep your car.
我有你的尊重就够了
Your respect is good enough for me.
对了 大表弟
Yo Cousin.
抱歉 毁了你的车
Sorry 'bout your car.
反正那车对我家人来说也是太慢了
Your's was too slow for a Torreto anyway.
你的英帕拉 你是当真的吗？
Your Impala. Are you serious?
《速度与激情8》
瞧你笑的样子
Look at that smile.
我就喜欢看你笑
I love it when you smile.
谁叫你招人开心呢
Make me happy.
我想是这地方让你开心
I think this place makes you happy.
它就好像能和你说话一样
It's like it speaks to you.
还记得那个小伙吗？曾经的车手和他父亲
You remember that guy? The Racer and his dad.
- 车上装船发动机那个 - 是啊！
- The one with the boat engine - Yeah!
- 是啊 - 当然记得
- Yeah - Of course.
我当时看着他们 我就…
I was looking at them, and I…
就忍不住在想象 你要是当爹会是什么样子
And I couldn't help but too imagine what you'd be like, if you were dad.
不不不 我还没怀孕呢
No, no, no… I'm not pregnant.
你想要一个吗？
Is that what you want?
这可不是我想要的 而是你想不想要
It's not about what I want or what you want…
之前我们没聊过这个问题
It's about why we haven't asked the question.
有什么可帮一手的吗？
Can I help you with that?
- 什么？- 需要帮忙吗？
- What? - You need a hand?
是 应该是需要
Yeah, I think I do.
这车好像是燃料不足了
Sounds like you're not getting any fuel.
是吧
Yeah.
可能是电磁阀出问题了 我看看能不能帮你修好
See if we can get some power into it.
怎么想到来古巴的？
What brings you to Cuba?
和其它人来这儿的原因一样吧
The same thing that brings everyone else to Cuba.
文化 人 美女
Culture People Beauty.
你为什么来到古巴呢？
What brings you to Cuba?
- 工作！- 星期五便服上班日
- Work! - Must be casual Friday.
蜜月过得还顺利吗 多姆
How is that honeymoon going Dom?
你的燃油继电器不见了
Your fuel relay is missing.
我知道
I know.
我很喜欢玩游戏 而且从没输过
I'd love to play games. Beaten the bests alone.
但我今天赶时间 你要是有话想说
I'm kinda in a rush, so if you got something to say…
这次的游戏可不太一样 我能向你保证
Oh this is a very different game that I can assure you.
这次？
This?
我要说的可是比游戏高级多的东西
There is something much greater at work here.
是你的命运
This is fate.
- 我自己的命运我自己创造 - 但今天不行
- I choose to make my own fate - Not today.
这就是你每天早上回公寓的路吗
This is the road you take to your apartment every morning.
看出了什么异样了吗 多姆？圣地亚哥饭店关门了
What else is different, Dom? The Santiago's closed?
你买古巴咖啡要多走两条街
Did you have to cross two blocks to go get your cuban coffee?
所以 最终是？黑咖啡 不加糖？
So, what is it? Black, no sugar?
对吧 为了今天见到你 我可做了很多工作
Yeah… I've put a lot of work into getting you here in today.
我已经在这了 你想要什么
Now that I'm here, what do you want?
我想让你为我工作
I want you to work for me.
为你工作？
Work for you?
早说还能省点时间呢
Well, I could have saved you a lot of time then.
看 我是不为任何人工作的
See, I don't work for anyone.
这回你躲不了 多姆
You can't walk away from this Dom.
现在不跟我谈 迟早也是要谈
We're gonna have this conversation one way or the other.
你看命运就是这么有趣
See that's the funny thing about fate.
它狡猾得很
It's cunning.
它能带给你美好
It can bring you beautiful things.
也能带给你接下来的这个时刻
and it can also bring you moments like this.
我听到你说会为我工作
I will hear that you want to work for me.
你会背叛你的兄弟
You're gonna betray your brothers.
抛弃你的原则 毁掉你的家庭
abandon your code, shatter your family.
看 你的团队…
See, your team…
即将面对他们唯一无法抗衡的东西
Is about to go up against the only thing they can't handle.
是什么呢？
What's that?
你
You.
对了 多姆 这事我不会跟任何人说的
Oh, and Dom, I wouldn't mention this to anyone.
（北纬34.1381 西经118.3534 上午9时）
他们会想进一切办法来攻击我们的
They are gonna be hitting us with everything they've got.
所以我们进攻的时候要全速前进
So, we wanna engage with maximum speed.
阻挡他们的进攻 然后直奔我们的目标而去
Neutralize the shooters and then move on to our objective.
有两件事我需要你们记住
There are two things I want you to keep in mind.
第一
Number one,
我选你们进这个队
I choose you for this squad.
是因为你们是这个星球上 最英勇的战士
because you are the most fearsome warriors on the planet.
第二
And number two,
上了战场就要竭尽所能的把它们全部干掉
You go out there, you do your job. And you take 'em down.
所有的人 都要达到这两点期望
Everyone… And I mean everyone…
我请你们到商场美甲及修脚
Manice and pedice at the mall.
待你们凯旋归来
Later on today.
准备好了吗
迈出脚步
摆开阵势 准备进攻
进攻
心怀感激并赞颂
这一方热土
心怀感激并赞颂这一方热土
为了我们的家人 不成功便成仁
用团结夺取胜利
冲啊 冲啊 冲啊
我们必胜
天呐
What?
我再也不想踢球了
I don't wanna play anymore.
好了 姑娘们加油 加油加油
Alright, let's go, girls. Let's go, let's go.
- 最后两分钟 - 你这亲友团阵容强大啊
- Final 2 minutes - Quite the cheering section.
是啊 妈妈们都来给孩子鼓劲了
Oh yeah. That's moms they come out to sport the kids.
不过妈妈好像比孩子还多
Except there seems to be more moms than kids,
而且多了不少
Way more like moms and…
没错 这里球迷基数大 加油 姑娘们
Yeah, it's a big soccer job. Let's go girls.
你的情报挺准的
So your intel was spot on…
那个在波斯湾失踪的电磁脉冲武器
A democly 7 EMP weapon that went missing in the gulf.
被解放阵线组织的军火贩子弄到了柏林
Arms dealer from the Liberation front have it in Berlin.
- 该死 - 电磁脉冲设备
- Shit - This thing can wipe out…
它可以让一个大城市的整个电网瘫痪
An entire electrical grid in a major city.
没有灯 没有电力 瞬间回到石器时代
No lights, no power, instant stone age.
寇伊 玛雅
Chloe, Maya…
别让她就那么跑了
You can't let her run by you like that.
- 动起来 动起来 - 霍布斯探员
- Let's go, let's go - Hey, Hobbs.
这是高级别大规模杀伤性武器
This is a class 4 WMD.
你知道这事情的严重性吗？
Do you have any idea what's at stake here?
我知道！我完全了解这事的严重性 好吧！
Yes! I know exactly what is at stake here, okay?
可我的红龙队这次要是输了
If Pink Butterflies beat my Red Dragon.
那就与冠军无缘了
that means we lose the championship.
然后我这20位小姑娘会哭的
Which means I have 20 little girls who are crying…
那可不是什么好事
And that's not a good thing.
因为这代表我得花时间在雪糕店上
Which then means I have to spend a lot of time in ice cream shops.
再带她们看蛋蛋的演唱会
and lot of time in Tay-Tay concerts.
- 蛋蛋是谁？- 泰勒·斯威夫特啊！
- Tay-Tay? - Yep? Taylor Swift.
你这是要急死我啊 给我省省心好吧
You gotta be shitting me get it together.
动起来 姑娘们
Let's go girls.
这事我们必须办
We need you to do this,
毕竟人命关天啊 但我话先说清楚了
Lot of lives are at stake. I need to be clear here.
美国政府不会以任何形式批准这次行动
US Government can not sanction this operation in anyway.
你得靠自己
You're on your own.
如果出了什么岔子 你就不只是被炒了
This thing goes sideways you don't just get burned,
还要坐牢去
you go to prison.
那样我们就没法把你弄出来了
And there's nothing we can do to get you out.
你先听我说好吗
Let me tell you something.
对我来说唯一比拯救苍生更重要的…
The only thing that I love more than saving lives…
就是我女儿
Is my daughter.
所以你最好别再跟我提政府的事情
So you don't shut up with this government bullshit right now.
拿出一点团队精神和尊重 送给我的红龙队
and start showing some team spirit and respect for the Red Dragons.
不然我就让20个姑娘排成队 挨个儿踢你的小蛋蛋
I'm gonna have all 20 of them lined up kick you right in the Tay-Tay.
加油 红龙队！
Go, Dragons!
再说一遍
Say it again.
- 加油 红龙队！- 对喽 伙计
- Go, Dragons! - Good boy.
红龙队 加油 红龙队 加油
Go Dragons… Go Dragons…
快 他有空挡 快 是了！
Go, he's open… Go, Yup!
太棒了！
Yes!
进球的那个就是我女儿！太棒了！
That is my daughter right there! Yes!
呀 真棒 快过来
Ah, yes, come here.
- 你真棒 - 干得好 孩子
- Awesome - Nice job.
老爸 又要去公干了
Daddy's gotta go to work?
是啊 爸爸又要去工作了
Oh yeah, daddy's gotta go to work.
那你需要个可以信赖的团队
Now, you gonna need to get a team that you can trust.
噢 我已经有团队了
Oh, I already got one.
- 嘻 多姆 - 嘻 霍布斯
- Hey, Dom - Hey, Hobbs.
有个柏林的活 需要兄弟你帮忙
We got a job in Berlin, and I need a favor, brother.
没问题
No problem.
我带着队伍跟你在柏林会合
I grab the team and meet you in Berlin.
谢谢你 稍后见
Thanks man. I'll see you soon.
（德国 柏林）
罗曼 你只需要引开他们就行了
You were only to supposed to create a diversion, Roman.
我刚不是引开了吗
That was a diversion.
你到底用了多大量的炸药啊？
How many of the damn explosives did you use?
我不知道 特尔佳 可能全用了！
I do not know, Tez. All of it?
- 等等 全用了？- 罗曼 老天爷！
- Wait, all of it? - Roman, Jesus!
- 天啊 - 前面还有一大波粉丝等着你呢
- Christ! - You have more of your fan club ahead.
他们还追着呢
They're still on us.
这些人是跟我们杠上了
These guys are taking this personal.
罗曼 我们刚炸了他们基地 还拿了电磁脉冲武器
Roman, we just blown up their facility and stole their EMP.
这性质就像体检时肛肠检查大夫
Other than your doctor's cold fingers,
拿手指捅你一样
I'd say it's about as personal as it can get.
- 进第二阶段 - 还有第二阶段？
- Phase 2 - Phase 2?
你还瞒到现在才说
So you just gonna keep that to yourself?
那啥是第一阶段？
What happen to Phase 1?
都干什么了？
What about that part?
是的 你还记得那飞机吗？
Yeah, remember the airplane?
除你之外 所有人都把车开出去了
Everyone drove their cars out but you.
我说了 是我引擎罢工了
I told you my engine seized up.
是你那颗小胆罢工了吧？
It's your balls that seized up?
跟着我做就行 好吗？
Just follow my lead, okay?
罗曼 你不管该做什么 别瞎琢磨
And Roman, whatever you do. Don't think.
特尔佳 可以放了
Tez, drop it.
重磅炸弹
Bomb's away.
队形分散！
Split now!
我的天啊！
Holy shit!
小心！
Look out!
- 是大铁球 特尔佳 - 跟你们说一声
- Great plan Tez - Just so you know.
还有漏网的
You miss some.
先耐心等等
I'll just wait for it.
真… 该死！
Oh… Shit!
我恨你 特尔佳！
I hate you, Tez!
吓到你了
Got your ass.
你没事吗？
You good?
任务结束后见
I'll see you when it's done.
好了 队友们都干得不错
Alright. Great job, team.
先就地解散 去安全的地方等我
Let's break up and meet me at the safe house.
干得漂亮 兄弟
Hell of a job, brother.
等回到基地 请你喝啤酒
When we can get back to the base. Beers on me.
你是疯了吗 托雷托！
You lost your god damn mind, Toretto!
托雷托 你碰那东西是要与我…
Toretto you put hands on that thing.
及世界为敌啊
you're gonna have the whole world coming for you including me.
我不知道你想干什么
I don't know what you're doing.
但你最好想清楚 托雷托
but you better think about this, Toretto.
现在放手还不算晚
It ain't too late to stop this.
现在晚了
It is now.
那个混蛋背叛了我们
That some bitch just crossed us…
什么？
What?
等等 你在说什么啊？
Wait a second, what are you talking about?
- 多姆拿走了电磁脉冲武器 - 胡说八道什么啊
- Dom took the EMP - Bullshit.
你人在哪儿？
Where are you?
我是来不及了 你们赶紧跑
It's too late for me. Get out of here.
他刚才那种眼神
Saw that look in his eyes.
我以前也曾见过
I've seen that look before.
多姆尼克·托雷托刚刚叛变了
Dominic Toretto just went rogue.
好了 我拿到了他的通话记录 各位
Alright, I got his phone records, y'all.
有很多来电无法查到号码
It's a whole bunch of calls to untraceable numbers.
一次性手机打来 是吗？
Burner phone, right?
不 是装了扰码器
Nah. Scrambled.
号码不变 但通过某种微型路由掩盖了信号踪迹
Same number but they got some sort of micro-router…
这意味着和多姆联系的人…
…to bury the signal path which means Dom is clearly…
远在我们的层次之上
…communicating with somebody that is above our pay grade.
看 虽然我不如你们了解多姆
Look, I do not know Dom as well as you,
但是我们还是面对现实吧
but if we just look at the facts.
多姆一直在和神秘人物
Dom's been having highly encrypted.
保持加密联系
conversation with some mysterious person.
他对霍布斯下手了
He took out Hobbs.
他偷走了武器 现在还失踪了
He stole the EMP, now he's disappeared.
所以你的意思是？
So what're you saying?
我们或许应该承认…
Maybe we should consider the fact that…
霍布斯是对的
Hobb's right.
多姆是真叛变了
Dom did go rogue.
- 莱蒂 - 当你要评判某人
- Letty - Before you judge the man,
请记得那个人曾救过你的命
Remember you're breathing now because he saved your life.
你就任凭她这么踩你
You just gonna let her bump your shoulder like that.
我的意思是说… 她那口气太冲了
I'm just saying it out…That was a little aggressive.
你干嘛 给她写邮件？
What're you gonna do. Email her?
没事啦
Chick…
（联邦顶级监狱）
不 不 且慢 各位
No no, wait, fellas.
谢谢
Thank you.
不错 这身新装扮可真带劲
Well, this is an exciting new look.
可裤子裆部总是有那么 有点紧
That's a little tight on the crotch as always.
这是哪个偶像天团拉来的？
What boyband bus did she fallen off?
这是我的新助手
My new junior associate.
和我一起负责这个案子 听你差遣
He's working with me on this. All yours.
无名氏先生和我
Mr Nobody and I.
有权限把你弄出去
have been given the authority to get you out of this.
你只需要接受我们的条件就能自由了
All you have to do is agree to the terms and you're free.
你这实习生说的条件是什么啊？
Restraining wills, talking about, what terms?
承认你在柏林的罪行
Confess to your crimes in Berlin.
叛国 从事国际间谍
Treason, international espionage.
大规模损坏公民财产
Massive destruction of civic property.
你照做 我们就能结案
You do that, we close the case.
然后呢？
And?
然后上国防安全黑名单 正好合德国心意
And the DSS blacklist. Sure Germany loves that.
你会正式成为罪犯
Officially you'll be a criminal.
噢…噢…噢
Woah, woah, woah.
你这表达能力得练练啊
You need to work on your delivery alright.
你是非正式的啊
Unofficially.
你跟我一起干 是不记录在案的
You're off the books. Come work with me.
- 我可不是罪犯 - 卢克 没事 就是个名号
- I'm not a criminal - Luke Come on. Labels.
我也不会认什么罪的
There is no confession.
我不接受私下交易
There are no back room deals.
我自己惹得事我自己会解决
Got myself into this, I'm gonna get myself out of it.
你知道的
You know that.
我知道 早跟他这么说了
I do and that's what I told them.
你看 这下满意了
Well, there you have it.
祝你庭审好运了
Good luck in the course, man!
你想过你女儿吗？
What about your daughter?
就算不为国家做事
You know, if you're not gonna do it your country,
至少也考虑下孩子
at least do it for your kid.
说错话了 孩子
Big mistake kid.
等等 卢克 卢克
Hold on. Look, look.
他还是用课本上那一套呢
He's still working from the manual.
我意思是 他连规矩都还没搞清楚
I mean, he doesn't even really know the rules.
算了 饶了他吧
Oh come on. Give him a break.
饶了我吧
Get a break.
卢克？
Luke?
这是谢谢了
I appreciate that.
- 见到你真高兴 无名氏 - 我也是
- It's good to see you, Nobody - You too.
先记住第一条
Rule No.1,
知己才能知彼
know your audience.
我给过你机会 你却搞砸了
I gave you your shot, you shit the bed.
现在我来示范正确的做法
Now I'm gonna show you how to get this done.
- 你死定了 警察！- 你死定了！
- You're dead cop! - Dead!
好哇 好哇 好哇…
Well, well, well…
卢克·霍布斯也蹲监狱了 都来瞧瞧啊？
Luke Hobbs behind bars. Would you look at that?
执法犯法 你也有今天
The band cop got it's day.
我说这颜色挺配你的
You know, that color looks good on you.
是啊 沾上点你的血就更配了
Yeah. Look a whole hell of a lot better with your blood on it.
祝你好运 我的大力神
Yeah. Good luck with that, Hercules.
警察干了坏事？
… gone bad. Huh?
真是没新意
Such a cliche.
对了 欢迎你入伙
Ah well. Welcome to the club.
你可别误解了 小子
I wouldn't get that twisted son.
我们不是一伙 也没什么共同点
We ain't in no club. We got nothing in common.
我不像你 我又不是来久住的
And unlike you, I ain't gonna be here long.
越狱你带铁锹了吗？
You bring the shovel did you?
这儿的钢筋混凝土有38英尺厚
Cause it's 38 feet of steel and concrete.
反正他们是这么说的？
What's up big dog?
要挖现在就动手吧
Better get to dig in.
你个白痴
You wanker.
是啊
Yeah.
让开
Move…
再说一遍
Say that again.
要是我再说一遍 那可就是对尸体说了
If I say it again, It will be to acorpse.
我倒是想体验一把
I'm going to enjoy this.
欢迎归来 多姆
Welcome back, Dom.
那边活儿干得漂亮
Nice job out there.
今晚很兴奋吧？
Excited about tonight?
这次你出马吗？
You're going on this?
你跟我来 多姆
You're with me Dom.
- 要给我看你的鞋柜子？- 没错
- Showing me your shoe collection? - Yup.
不同场合都有款合适的
A pair for every occasion.
你的枪够装备一支小军队的了
There's enough guns here to outfit a small army. Huh?
这些还只是冰山一角呢
Oh this is just the tip of the iceberg.
你知道我喜欢你哪儿吗 多姆
You know what I like about you, Dom.
你是个真正的亡命徒
You're a genuine outlaw.
你是按自己的规矩出牌
I mean, you're a man who lives by his own rules.
但让我惊讶的是 之前我们在古巴
Which was surprising because when I saw you in Cuba, I heard about a.
我听说某人差点用摩托车把你给弄死
guy who almost killed you with a motorcycle and.
而你却没有拿走他的车？
you… let him keep his car?
- 噢 你是不是挺纳闷的？- 嗯哼
- Oh, that confused you? - Hmm.
当然我可以拿走他的车
Of course I could've taken his car.
但我不拿 意义更大
But it's about something bigger.
我这么做
This way…
能改变他们
I changed them.
但你没有那个义务啊
That's not your responsibility.
- 但我人就这样 - 是吗
- That's who I am - Is it?
那我问你个问题 多姆 你一生什么是最重要的
Let me ask you something Dom, what's the best thing in your life?
- 是家人 - 不 不是
- Family - No, it's not.
这不是你真实想法？
But if you're being honest?
你最在意的是每次飚车的那十秒种
It's the 10 seconds between.
那十秒里你什么都不想
start and finish, when you're not thinking about anything.
没有你的家人 更没有责任 只有你自己
No family, not obligations, just you.
那意味着自由
Being free.
我必须告诉你 你最近忙着拯救世界
I gotta tell you. This whole saving the world…
跟罗宾汉一样是没有意义的
Robin Hood nonsense you've been doing recently…
那些都是胡扯 那不是你
It's bullshit. It's not you.
做回真实的自己吧
Be who you are.
那样你可以快活一辈子
Why live only a quarter mile at a time,
不用依赖飚车那短暂一瞬间
when you can live your whole life that way?
你那一身肌肉就这点本事
See all those blow that muscles will give you.
花拳绣腿有什么用处
All show and no…
我这用处多着呢
Well I got plenty of goal.
你是记忆错位了吧
You must have misplaced that.
当时是我把你打得屁滚尿流 从楼上扔下去
When I kicked your ass up in down that office of yours.
是啊
Yeah.
胡编乱造不也是你们英国人特色吗？
Just like you Brits, rewriting History, huh?
反正我只记得被扔出…
All I know. It was not me who was thrown out.
四楼窗户的人不是我
of a 4 storey window.
我自己跳的 是我从四楼窗户跳下去
Jumped. I jumped out of a 4 storey window.
救我搭档的命
Saving my partner's life.
在我们国家
Because where I'm from,
我们打架从来不会用上扔炸弹
we don't settle fight by throwing bombs.
好呀 真搞笑 这就是我的国家
Well, that's funny, because where I'm from,
还不需要女人来救男人呢
we don't need women to run to our rescue.
我意思是 你相信跟前的你
I mean, do you really believe you could stand in front of me?
凭赤手空拳就能击败我吗？
And beat me in a straight up old fashioned fist fight?
那你给我听着 你和我…
Let me tell you something. Me and you…
一对一单挑 谁都不许找帮手
One on one, no one else around.
你的小屁股等着开花吧 揍你我就跟打手鼓一样
I will beat your ass like a Cherokee drum.
没准哪天我们可以试试
Maybe one day we will find that out.
噢 你就祈祷那一天永不到来吧
Oh, you better hope that day never comes.
我说过不行 无名氏先生
I said no, Mr. Nobody.
我不会离开这牢房的
I'm not leaving this cell.
我会用自己方法出去的
I'll get out my way.
还是正道的办法
The right way.
- 快回牢房去 - 门只是出点故障
- Get back to your cell - It's just a malfunction.
- 快退下！- 只是故障而已啊
- Get back! - Just a malfunction.
别让他跑了
Don't let him get away.
霍布斯！
Hobbs!
我等这一天已经很久了
I've been waiting a long time for this.
那就接着等 贱人！
Keep waiting bitch!
用橡皮弹是个大错误
Rubber bullets, big mistake.
呀 比我预想的时间要久一点
Ah, took longer than I expected.
- 我有两个问题 - 是
- 2 questions - Yeah.
- 我女儿呢？- 在你妹那儿
- My daughter? - With your sister.
- 托雷托呢？- 你问这个有点意思
- Toretto? - That's interesting you ask.
这是我的新基地 欢迎来到无名之地
This is my new base, welcome to Nowhere.
你这创意太贫乏了
Nice little stair for you.
听着 我待会有事要跟你说
Listen, It's something I don't wanna talk to you about…
听着各位 感谢大家
Hey, listen guys. Thanks…
我说怎么上铐子了 搞什么啊？
Whoa, whoa, what handcuff. What is this?
这就是滥用权力
It's called the abuse of power.
你说把他们关一起的
You told me to round 'em up.
我又没让你铐住
I told you that… hand…
给他们解开 老天爷 我真太尴尬了
Cut 'em loose. Oh man, this is embarrassing.
真对不起各位 我真的
I'm sorry guys, what do I have?
你就这么对待老朋友？
This is how you treat old friends?
朋友？
Friend?
我们还不知道这家伙真实身份呢
We don't even really know who the hell this guys is.
我是谁不重要 特尔佳 我就是个无名氏啊
It does not matter who I am, Tez I'm like Nobody ok?
无名氏 那他是谁？
Nobody, then who is he?
他什么都不是 还不如我呢
He's nothing he's like less than me.
我们这是和无名氏待在无名之地啊
Clearly we're getting nowhere, with nobody.
我在这待了四个小时 饿的前胸贴后背
I've been in here for 4 hours, my ribs are sore.
不管你们怎么想 反正我要走了
I don't know about y'all, but I'm out.
- 建议你最好别走 - 什么？
- I wouldn't recommend that - What?
因为你们刚砸了柏林那一票
Well, thanks to your bust Berlin job.
进入国际刑警组织通缉犯前十名
You all made interpol's top 10 most wanted list.
前十名 还真不赖啊
Top 10? Uh-huh. That's alright.
不包括你 罗曼
Well, not you.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
你就差一点 你第十一名
You just missed the cut, you're number 11.
- 所以 - 就我没排进去？
- So - I missed it?
- 对啊 - 这不可能
- Yeah - That's impossible.
那他们都排第几啊？
What number did they come in at?
他六 他八 他九…
Six, eight, nine…
她十
Ten.
她是第十？不可能 她怎么可能第十
She's Ten? That's impossible, there is no way she's at 10.
噢 她绝对可以第十
Oh, She's definitely at 10.
我们来关注一个
How about we focus on someone who.
不会出现在任何名单上的人吧？
we're not gonna find out in anybody's list?
最终确认还要等
We are awaiting hard confirmation, but…
但我相信她是那个网络恐怖分子
I believe that's the cyber terrorist known as Cipher.
不 等下 塞弗是一个组织
Wait, no, Cipher's an organization.
可不是一个人
Not a person.
我们的线报可不是这样
Not according to our sources.
- 她想干什么？- 不知道啊
- What does she want? - I don't know.
塞弗在黑客界地位就像上帝
Cipher is like a digital active God.
这个组织 不 这个人 能从暗处操纵全世界的系统
They, she, can manipulate world systems under shadows.
能被黑的地方都任凭其摆布
Anything that can be hacked…
而且蹊跷的是…
And here is the kicker.
你永远找不到她的操作痕迹
You will never find her linked to any other.
她在网络世界每过几秒钟就清一次痕迹
Her digital identity is scrubbed every few seconds worldwide.
所以她就是那个终极大反派
So basically, she is the boogeyman.
是的 她是
Yeah, she is.
只可惜她是我见过的最性感的大反派
One of the hottest boogeyman I have ever seen, I mean…
你们谁认识她 告诉她快来找哥哥我
If y'all know her, tell her to get extra boy.
- 你十二岁吗？- 你踢到我小腿了
- What are you, 12? - That was my scene.
那这么说吧
Let's just say.
人们害怕匿名的黑客组织
People are scared of the hacker group Anonymous.
但匿名组织也不敢惹她
But even anonymous won't mess with her.
那这些到底由和我们有什么关系啊？
What the hell does any of this have to do with us?
是没多少关系 莱蒂 但…
Probably nothing, Letty. But…
我发现了一件有趣的事
I do find it interesting, apparently for some reason.
就是她不知为何正在和这个家伙合作
She's now working with this guy.
他把一个随时能用的电磁脉冲武器交到她手上
He's already delivered a fully operational EMP into her hands.
使用这种武器
Detonate that,
她可以让整座城市陷入战争火海
they can turn any city in the world into a war zone.
那你建议我们怎么做呢？
So then what is it that you're suggesting?
要不先找到多姆？
Maybe we find Dom huh?
首先我们抓住他 然后弄明白…
Well, first let's catch him and then figure out.
- 他为什么叛变 - 所以你要我们来…
- why he's turned - So y'all want us…
找到多姆
To track Dom.
罗曼 我知道这个活儿不简单
And I know Roman, it's kinda a big job.
- 这压根就不可行 - 没错 所以我呢…
- It's impossible - Which is why…
给你们又找了一个帮手
I'm bringing in an extra pair of hands.
我这一天过得可真超值啊
Ah. My day just got a whole hell of a lot better.
无名氏先生 你能告诉我 为什么请来这位…
Mr. Nobody you want to tell me why you just put me in a room.
爱喝下午茶的下三滥到我眼前晃悠
with this teen crumpeting criminal, some bitch.
你这小脑萎缩的大嘴巴
You got a big mouth on a small head.
我记得你的犯人编号是6753
Coming from prisoner 6753.
别以为我们忘了你干的好事
Don't think we've forgotten everything that you've done.
我们永远不会和这个家伙一伙
We're not… teaming up with this guy.
先把话说清楚
Let's get one thing clear.
我不加入你的团队 我才不在乎你…
I ain't on your team. I don't care about you, you crew…
你们团队成员或是所谓的大家庭 我冲塞弗来的
Your little family. I'm here for Cipher.
你这混蛋要干嘛 来应聘吗？
You gonna do apply for a job, Head-asshole?
你这件紧身T恤
You don't think that tight t-shirt.
好像阻碍你大脑供血
is cutting off the circulation to your brain.
该买大一号的啊
You should get bigger size.
是塞弗先找上我的
Cipher came to me first.
她想让我帮她偷龙葵
Wanted me to steal Nightshade for her.
我拒绝后她就盯上我弟弟
When I said no, she went off to my brother.
对啊
Oh Yes.
欧文兄弟 怎么能忘了他呢啊？
Brother Owen who could forget him?
他之前到处惹是生非
Former hell-raiser and current guest,
目前在一个秘密的监牢里服刑
at a nasty little black site prison.
塞弗毁了他 留下他等死
Cipher corrupted him left him for dead.
所以如果有机会干掉她
So if I get a shot to take her down,
相信我 我一定会抓住她
believe me, flicks I'm taking it.
你抓我的鞋堵你屁股吧
You're taking my boot right up your ass.
两位两位 找塞弗最快的途径就会通过托雷托
Guys, guys, guys. The fastest way to find Cipher is through Toretto.
现在除了我 这世上只有两个人
Now aside from myself, there's only two men in the world,
曾成功追踪到他的下落
that have ever managed to actually track him down with any success.
而且怎么着
And guess what.
这俩人现在都站在我面前 随你们乐不乐意
They're both standing in front of me right now. So like it or not,
你们俩要一起合作
You two are gonna work together.
都明白了吗？
You got that?
我就当是同意了
I'm gonna take that as a yes.
只有我一个人明白了吗？
Am I the only one seeing this?
噢 这下子好了
Oh, this oughtta be good.
我说 用天眼系统 我们冒着生命危险
Use God's eye. We put our lives on the line…
满世界地去找人
Running around the world trying to figure this thing out.
而天眼能找到任何人 对吧 用它找多姆不就得了
It can find anybody, right? Let's use it to find Dom.
罗曼 这真是个好主意
Roman, that is a great idea.
听到了吗？是个好主意
Did you hear that? Great idea.
- 喂喂喂 假装没听见 - 无名氏先生
- And no, no! No pointing out - Mr. Nobody.
我们开始吧
Let's fire it up… huh?
找到了 他在伦敦
Got him. He's in London.
是的
Yeah.
等等 第二处定位到香港了
Wait, we have got a 2nd match in Hong Kong.
- 对 还有个在首尔 - 还有东京
- Bejing and Seole - And Tokyo.
搜索结果差不多覆盖全球各大城市了
And just about every other major city on the planet.
所以我们呢 首先会想到的是使用天眼系统
And so… God's eye was where we start.
但塞弗已经巧妙掩盖他们实际位置所在…
Cipher's already created an evasion that masked her location by…
向全球的随机地点发信息包
Pinging random spots all over the globe.
不过你的想法不错啦 罗曼
But it was a good thought Roman.
她这让我的软件成了摆设
So she's made my programme obsolete.
拉姆齐
And that Ramsey…
所以我们请你来啊
is why are you here.
走快捷方式在这里行不通的 小滑头
See, simple solutions aren't gonna cut it here slick.
你说这话干嘛看着我啊？
Why are you looking at me when you're saying that?
等等 等下 等一下
Wait a second, wait, wait.
这儿没准真有快捷方式可走呢
Simple solutions might just cut it.
你看他们为了让天眼发出虚拟信息包
In order for God's eyes to give up all this false pings,
用了通量逻辑组件数组
Means they have to be using a free relay.
听他俩怎么说
Watch these two.
也就是说肯定有一个同步随机数发生器
Which means it has a decaying sync quantanizer.
我们可以反过来利用
Which we can reverse.
追踪到信号源头
And track it back to the originating source.
并找到多姆的真实位置
and find Dom's true location.
瞧瞧 他们有真本事
Telling you, they got skills.
我就是这意思
That was my idea.
我刚才就这么说的 记得吗？
That's what I was saying, remember in there?
好了 我们试试吧
Alright. Let's try this.
起作用了
It's working…
翻翻你的教科书 组织力量响应吧
Time you wanna take your manual and start organizing first response…
立刻联系这地区部署的国际警力
Let's get a hold of our international…
仍然是新手
He's still green.
是啊 闻到婴儿尿片味儿了
Yes, like first baby shit.
一旦追踪到位置
Yes, we've tried those location…
立即行动
…wanna mobilize.
立即联系一个更好的混蛋 没人尊重你 就位
Let's get a hold of a, better asshole. No one respects you, over.
离我远一点
Get away from me.
好的 他们不在中国
Alright they are not in China…
也不在俄罗斯
or Russia.
欧洲排除了
Europe's clear.
但这一处还不能排除
But this one's not going away.
这有意思了
This is interesting.
为什么？
Why?
因为他们就在这儿
Because that's here.
这个你们都喜欢吗 这是新一代脑震荡手榴弹
Did you all enjoy that? Next generation concussion grenade.
他扰乱你们的感官
It scrambles your senses.
别怕 一小时后会失效的
Don't worry, It'll wear off in an hour.
差不多吧
Probably.
你好啊 戴克 很高兴又见面了
Hello, Deckard. Nice to see you again.
快看啊 多姆你人刚没走一会
Look at this, bodies not even cold Dom.
你的家人就找人来替代你了
Your family's already replacing you.
你选了个必输的团队
You chose the loosing team.
我就说你弟弟比你精多了
I guess your brother is smarter than you.
（欧文·肖）
往主框架嵌入天眼真是聪明
Smart move embedding God's eye into the mainframe.
害得我大老远跑一趟
Irritating to make me have to come.
来把它收拾了
all the way down here to get it, but.
我们走吧
Let's go.
多姆！
Dom!
你真的要背叛你的家人吗？
You're gonna turn your back on family?
就现在这样吗？
Just like that?
我们走
Let's go.
你没事吧？
You okay?
那不是他
That wasn't him.
那女的不知怎么着他的
I don't know what she's got on him.
但那不是多姆
But that wasn't Dom.
- 布莱恩知道该怎么做 - 不行
- Bryan would know what to do - No.
不能把布莱恩和米娅再扯进来
We can't bring Bryan and Mia into this.
不都说好了嘛
We agreed on that.
我知道
I know.
刚才那一下 是做给她看
Back there was that for her,
给我看 还是给你做自己？
for me, or you?
而且有那个必要吗？
Or was it either necessary?
你说有必要吗？
Necessary?
没什么东西是必要的 一切不过是选择而已
Nothing is necessary. Everything is a choice.
我只是做个选择 你也一样啊
I simply made one but so did you.
你本可以拦我 但你选择不拦
You could have stopped me, but you chose not to do.
我很好奇莱蒂会怎么想
I wonder what Letty thought about that.
你踩住老虎的的脖子…
The problem of putting your foot on a Tiger's neck…
麻烦在于你永远都不能抬脚
is you can never let it up.
你选择来这的原因 我要提醒你一下
I think I need to remind you why you chose to be here.
埃琳娜
Elena.
多姆
Dom.
真对不起
Sorry.
你就不应该来这儿
You shoudn't have come.
没什么能阻止我来
Nothing's gonna get me away.
现在我们三个都在她手上
Now she has the three of us.
想看看他吗？
You wanna see him?
来看爸爸
See papa.
爸爸
Papa.
当我知道自己怀孕的时候
When I realized I was pregnant.
你刚好发现莱蒂还活着
You had just find out Letty was alive.
所以我决定等莱蒂和你度蜜月回来
So I decided when Letty and you go back from your honeymoon.
再告诉你孩子的事
I was going to tell you.
然后我还没有机会 就被她抓了
And then she took us before I had the chance.
他起名字了吗？
have a name?
我起的叫马科斯
I call him Michaels.
但那是他的中间名
That his middle name.
他大名应该由他爸爸来取
I thought his father should give him first name.
我很抱歉 多姆
I'm sorry, Dom.
你没什么好抱歉的
There is nothing to be sorry for.
不管发生什么事…
Whatever happens…
都要保住我们的儿子
Just save our son.
你的儿子
Your son.
探视可好？
Good visit?
我知 我知道你在想什么
I know. I know what you're thinking.
我把警卫都支开了
I just let the guards go,
所以你在这房间只有两个对手
so there is only two opponents in the room.
罗兹他有枪 所以你会想到先干掉他 我了解你
Rhodes has the gun, so you'll take him out first, I know you.
然后你会想到
And then you're thinking.
埃琳娜是个警察 没准你们俩
Elena is a cop, maybe the two of you.
能一起从这儿冲出去
can fight your way out of here.
你要想的事太多了
So much to think about.
那我还是帮你一把吧
Let me make it easier for you.
你想怎么来就怎么来
Do with it as you wish.
听过选择理论吗 多姆？
Have you heard of choice theory Dom?
这理论有很多公式
There's a bunch of axiems.
但有两点需要你结合自身考虑
but only two you really need to concern yourself with,
其一 我们只能控制自己的行为
One. The only person's behavior we can control is our own.
其二 我们唯一能给对方的东西是信息
And two, the only thing we can truly give another person is information,
所以我给你一些信息
so let me give you some.
看到这里的摄像头了吗？
You see this cameras in here?
一旦你敢轻举妄动
The moment you make a move,
立刻会有携带
highly paid men with weapons,
武器的人冲进来
will make there way into this room.
执行一条具体指令
With one very… specific instruction.
他们不是要救我
It's not to save me.
是要杀了你儿子
It's to kill your son.
到时候可是枪林弹雨
And that's a lot of bullets.
只需要一颗子弹就能让你失去一切
And it only takes one for you to loose everything.
我之所以丑话说在前头
So, I have to ask you, because…
因为我知道家庭对你多重要
I know family is so important to you.
你真的想做出那个选择吗？
Is that really a choice you wanna make?
如果是的话 我准备好了
Because I'm ready as you are.
老天知道我多么想扣下这扳机
I pull this trigger, and God knows I wanna…
可就算杀光飞机上所有人…
I'll kill everyone on this plane…
我还是救不出她俩母子
I still couldn't get in there.
因为你这儿是双人自动防故障系统
Cause you here manipulate this system.
就我一个人打不开的
Since I'm alone!
我根本没得选择！
I got no choice!
我想未必
I don't think so.
你想看看以前的多姆吗？
You want to see the old Dom?
看好了
Watch.
去死吧
Shit.
做个好梦
Sweet dream.
真该死
Damn it…
她全删掉了 还拿走天眼
She wiped it off. Took God's eye.
那是唯一能找到他们的东西
That was the one thing we could use to find him.
我们一无所有了
We lost everything.
- 怎么样了 公主？- 快找到托雷托了
- Yeah, princess? - Find it to rail.
不过我还能抽出几分钟时间来
But I've got couple of minutes to spare.
如果你需要 我可以再次把你送进医院
If you want me to send you to the hospital again.
- 小子！- 首先啊
- Yo Rules! - First off,
- 这不是我名字 - 那就小无名氏
- That's not my name - Little nobody.
- 别这么叫我 - 就叫这个名字吧
- Don't call me that - Oh that's definitely stinky.
你帮我告诉那边那位殿下
Great do me a favor, and tell your majesty over there,
我们会找到托雷托 会作为一个团队 找到他的
that we're gonna find Toretto. We find Toretto together as a team.
等一切结束后
When this is all over,
我很乐意给他来一顿抽耳刮子
you have me to slap that whickest biscuit right off his face.
等下各位 我想戴克可能摸到门了
Wait a minute, guys. I think Decker's actually onto something.
想想多姆和塞弗
How do you think Dom and Cipher got.
是怎么骗过我们入境的呢？
into the country without us knowing?
- 坐幽灵航班 - 我以为无法追踪的飞机…
- Ghost flights - That untraceable aircraft.
只是个互联网骗局
it was all internet conspiracy stuff.
还真不是
It's not.
卫星和雷达网络覆盖地球各个角落
Satellites and radar grids…
而且会动
All across the globe shift.
像洋流一样 他们的频道有的开有的关
Like an ocean. And they've got channels that open and close.
理论上
And theoretically,
你只要找到熟悉规律的人
if you know the right people who Know the right patterns.
你就能在盲区里飞行
You can fly right through the blind's box…
且能够躲过探测
can't be intercepted.
所以你知道多姆要去哪吗？
So you know where Dom is headed?
是的 纽约
Yeah, New York.
看到了吗 卢克
You see there Luke…
你们会相处得很好的
You guys… are gonna get along just great.
这也验证了 这第二条规则 你永远不会失去一切
Which proves, rule number two, you never lose everything.
直升机待命
Fire up the chopper.
好了 各位 祝纽约之行玩的尽兴
Guys, have a bowl and a Big Apple.
（纽约）
谁能说说我们为什么要这样出行？
Are we travelling like this again?
因为我们没有天眼 必须躲开监控网
Because Dom took God's Eye, so we need to stay off the grid.
可至于这样吗？
But like this?
在我呕吐之前问你个问题 兄弟
Look here man. Before I throw up in my mouth…
我们到底来这干嘛？
Let me ask you what are we doing here?
问得好 罗曼
That's a good question, Roman.
我来回答你
Let me show you.
欢迎来到我们的新行动基地
Welcome to our new base of operations.
我没开玩笑啊 这是个什么地方？
Now seriously, what is this place?
这里可是天堂啊
This… is heaven.
这是局下属车库 绰号叫玩具店
The agency garage. We call it the toy shop.
我们从东海岸毒枭那儿
This is where we house every vehicles.
缴获的车全部在这里
seized from drug dealers of East coast.
而且 无名氏先生都说了
Now. Mr nobody said…
如果我们想找到多姆
If we're gonna have a chance of catching Dom…
首先必须要够快
We're gonna have to be damn fast.
这应该能有用
Maybe this could help.
我们这辆坦克 有750马力
We got a tank. 750 horsepower.
配6.6升V8通用产发动机
6.6 liter V8 Duramax engine.
顶部配备M153远程操作武器台
With the M153 probe remotely operated weapon station on top.
这不是从毒贩那儿弄的吧
You didn't get this from drug dealers.
不 那个嘛
No. No that…
那个是向美国军队借的
United State's army weaponry.
军队研究这种武器
See the army developing machines like this.
是要让士兵在一英里外操控好 保证生命安全
the soldiers could drive from a mile way so they can stay safe and alive.
不过好在
But luckily…
里头配备有备用驾驶座
There is a back up driver seat.
适合我们这种喜欢上手的人
for those of us who like to get more hands on.
我坐在里面会觉得这东西
I'm sitting there wondering this whole time when this thing feeling badly.
就像芝士工厂配的门童
and she's getting fact.
谁都不可以对它亲自上手 这不能开到大马路上
No one is getting hands on it. She doesn't go on some streets.
我心动了
I'm in love.
这个也不行 不行 这是百万美元的样车
Again? No. No… That's a million dollar show car.
我们不能太招摇
The point is to not draw attention.
就是要搞逆向思维
It's reverse psychology.
多姆绝不会料到的
Dom will never see it coming.
这车是荧光橙色
It's neon orange,
连国际空间站都能看得见
The international space station would see it coming.
你就不能随便选一个不那么扎眼的吗
Go choose anything less inspeculous.
不不不 这制动卡盘 太不可思议了
No no no. This is ridiculous. Hey my man,
伙计 车你放那就行了
You can put that down right there.
这是一件礼物 给我的礼物
This is a gift. A real gift.
我知道你要干什么
I know what you're doing.
我喜欢你的胡子 你就是圣诞老人
I like your beard. You're blanta.
还是黑人版的？
Black santa?
我没开玩笑 把车放那儿
No, I'm serious. Put it down right here…
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
发动机打不着火了 我得检查下
Engine's mis-firing, I gotta check it out.
不 这不属于计划内 多姆
No. That's not part of the plan, Dom.
那可不是
Clearly…
但你总不想因为发动机坏了事吧
But unless you want the engine to cease on the job,
给你五分钟时间
You have five minutes.
再调一下镜头给我
I want another visual.
有个取款机能用
I got an ATM.
这样子可不行
I don't like this.
我要看到托雷托
I want to see Toretto.
没有别的摄像头了
There are no more cameras.
那就找点别的
Then find something.
能反光的东西 哪怕是后视镜都行
Punch in on something reflective A car mirror, anything…
- 知道我是谁吗？- 就为这个来的
- You know who I am? - That's why I'm here.
知道我的本事吗
You know what I'm capable of.
我就为这个来的
It's why I'm here.
我喝完这杯茶再跟你说
I'll give you until I finish my cup up.
我都要渴死了
And I'm fucking thirsty.
我有自己的节奏 不会浪费你时间的
I got limited time. So won't take up too much of yours.
不 不
Oh no.
我有价值的东西早被你榨取光了 托雷托先生
No, you've already taken everything I have of value, Mr. Toretto,
你还想怎样呢？
What more could you possibly want?
我想回报你
To give you something back.
跟我说话啊
Talk to me.
这儿有点不对劲
Something's not right here.
我第一次见我儿子时…
First time I saw my son…
他在防弹玻璃后面
was behind a bulletproof glass.
当他向我伸出手 我却无法抱着他
When he reached me, I couldn't hold on.
这是我最心痛的事
It's the worst pain I ever felt…
我知道你完全能体会其中的滋味
I know you know exactly how that feels.
我们或许能改变这一切
Maybe we could change that…
我先警告你 我认为
And I warn you, I think…
你提出一个非常危险的建议 托雷托先生
You are about to suggest something really dodgy Mr Toretto.
我就为这个来的
It's why I'm here.
我的天 给我再凑近点来
Just punch in on something, I'm not liking this.
我不喜欢这样 就觉得不对劲
Something is not right.
- 罗兹 快有了吧？- 对
- Rhodes, you close? - Yeah.
- 推上去 - 那送货车要走了
- Go - The delivery truck's moving.
第五大道那边目前有安排执勤 问题不大
继续安排巡逻 排查险情
戴克·肖 上尉
Captain Deckard Shaw,
以不顾生命危险
distinguished himself by acts of gallantry.
远超职责要求的英勇行为脱颖而出
of the risk of his life above and beyond the call of duty.
他的勇敢行动 拯救了人质和战友的生命
His bold actions saved the lives of hostages and his team mates.
建议授予 维多利亚十字勋章
Recommendation: Victoria Cross.
这是英国政府授予的最高荣誉
Highest honor the British Government has ever given.
他还是个叛徒
To a traitor.
这整件事在我看来有些说不通
Some about this old thing just doesn't add up to me.
这种事情可是无独有偶吧
Well then don't do the same kind of funny math,
某被授予银星的美国军方探员还盗窃电磁脉冲武器呢
It says a DSS agent who has a soul to stop a valid stolen EMP.
听着熟悉吧？
Sound familiar huh?
能过来帮个忙吗？
Wanna give me a hand?
- 数三下 - 好
- On three? - Yeah.
一二三 走
One two…
你知道吗 要是再活一次
You know, you can tell this in another letter…
我俩肯定能干一番事业
But maybe we could've caused some serious damage.
- 是啊 我们有可能 - 对吧
- Yes, we could have - Yeah.
可惜等这完事了
Shame I'll have to punch you,
我会把你脑壳摔烂
head of defend, when this is all over.
好吧 恕我直言 上尉
Ah well. With all due respect, Captain,
等这一切结束了我俩找个地方
When this whole thing is over we're gonna find a location.
我会把你牙打到嗓子眼去
and I'm gonna knock your teeth so far down your throat.
以后刷牙就只能从屁眼进去了
You're gonna stick a toothbrush right up in your ass to brush up.
给我接上天眼
Give me God's eyes.
- 天眼已启动 - 很好
- God's eye active - Thanks.
找找那俄罗斯人
Let's find us some Russian.
我的小眼睛请仔细搜寻
That spy with my little lie…
那位国防部长在哪里
Minister of defense.
我们九点钟在莫斯科降落
We land back in Moscow by nine.
这是最新的防务报告 有昨天汇报的所有要点
Here's the latest defense report, All the items in yesterday's meet.
坐标上传到多姆的导航系统
Upload this coordinates to Dom's nav.
收到
Copy that.
他在车队第三辆车里
He's in the third car.
是一辆豪华装甲轿车
It's a guard class limousine.
我的团队呢？
Where's my team?
- 他的团队呢？- 还没发现任何踪迹
- Where's his team? - There's no sign of 'em yet.
不在监控网里
They are off the grid.
可能躲在什么地方了
Probably just bunker down somewhere.
我们正在逼近了
Closing in on him.
你们准备好了吗？
You guys ready?
有一点我可以保证 多姆
One thing I can guarantee you Dom.
没人料到会有这出
No one's ready for this.
我要利用和操纵车队方圆两英里内
I want every with chip with the GEODIE exploits.
每辆车的芯片漏洞
in a two mile radius around that motorcade now.
有一千多辆呢
There's over a thousands of them.
全给我黑掉
Hack 'em all.
（纽约）
（自动驾驶启动）
请殭尸车登场
It's zombie time.
（目标已控制）
（安全限制解除）
我要是你 就会系好安全带
I'd buckle up if I were you.
自动驾驶激活
AUTO-DRIVE ACTIVATED.
（防撞功能已禁用）
安全传感器已被控制
Safe systems are released.
谢谢
Thankyou.
嘻！
Hey!
给我瞄准车队
Target the motorcade.
现在 好戏要上演了
And here they come.
怎么回事？
What is going on?
好痛啊
Ouch.
快开走！
Drive fast!
警方护卫车搞定
Police escort down.
干掉领头和跟随的车
Take out the lead and follow cars.
快开！快开！
Drive! Drive!
- 又干掉两辆 - 前面还有一辆
- Two more down - There's still a warranty.
我们前面还有一辆 朝发动机开火
There's more cars ahead of us. Shoot their engines.
我的天啊！
Oh God!
有一大群车辆在自动驾驶
We got an army of cars driving themselves.
请求支持！特种部队支援！
Send backup! Send S.W.A.T!
哪怕你们派童子军也行
I don't care if you send the goddamn boy scout…
请给点帮忙
Just send up some help!
这才是多姆
Now that's Dom.
快点开走 快点开走！
Faster, faster!
车队刚拐到第七大道
The motorcade just turned on 7th.
很好 把动静闹大
Perfect. Make it rain.
这不好玩
That's not funny.
目标已无法移动
Target immobilized.
该你了 多姆
You are up Dom.
- 那是怎么回事？- 他要干什么？
- Who the hell is that? - What is he doing?
你在等什么啊？
What the hell are you waiting for?
朝他射击！
Shoot him!
快啊 快啊 快啊！
Come on, come on!
没子弹了
I'm out.
该死
Shit.
别担心 先生 车是防弹的
Don't worry sir. This car is bulletproof.
你在里面很安全
You'll be safe in here.
- 把手提箱给我 - 把手提箱给他
- Give me the case - Give him the case.
里头有核弹发射密码啊 我们决不能给他
These are nuclear launch codes. We cannot give it to him.
他要干什么？
What is he doing now?
油箱被锯穿了
He just cut a hole in our gas tank.
漂亮 多姆
Good work, Dom.
在会合点等你
Meet you at the pick-up.
我找到我的团队了
I think I know where my team's at.
- 在哪？- 就在我眼前
- Where? - Right in front of me.
他们冲你来的 快离开 多姆
This is on you. Get out of there, Dom.
各位 我知道多姆为何而来了
Guys, I know why Dom's here.
警方说他抢了个核密码箱
Police scanners are saying he's stolen Nuclear Football.
结束了 托雷托 给我从车里滚出来
It's over, Toretto. Get your ass out of the car now.
你还想玩是吧？
That's how you wanna play this?
那就玩吧
Let's play.
别这样 多姆
Don't do this, Dom.
他是想跑
He got run.
- 你要干什么？- 这是陷阱！
- What're you doing? - It's a trap!
该死
Damn.
现在我理解追我们那些警察的感受了
Now I know what it feels like be every cop ever chasing us.
我再靠近一点 把他别住
I'm gonna get a little close and I ped him.
噢 你还想把多姆逼停？
Oh, so you just gonna take Dom?
小无名氏看来是彻底疯了啊
Little Nobody has clearly lost his little mind.
我搞定他
I'm on him.
别急 要团队协作
Easy, work together.
- 小心慢着！- 慢着 慢着 慢着！
- Look out! - Wait, wait, wait!
坏了
Oh shit.
我去抄近道
I will take the short cut.
小心！别撞着人
Look out! Watch these people.
哥哥我来了！
Big Sexy coming through!
这回你别想跑 多姆
Not this time, Dom.
小心开车！不然缆绳会断掉！
Watch drive! Or the line will snap!
拉他出来 控制住他
Stretch him out. Hold them.
他那破车估计得用2000马力
He gotta have about 2000 Horse Power in that thing.
试试3000马力
Try 3000…
试试5000吧
Try Five.
赶紧离开那儿
Get out of there.
我在想办法呢
I'm working on it.
别琢磨了 动手就是了
Stop working on it, and do it…
不不不 这可是我的宾利啊
No, no no… It's my Bentley.
不！不！
No! No!
拿着手提箱 赶紧走！
Get that case and run!
快跑啊！
Move!
人们还以为这就是街头火拚
They thought… this was gonna be a streetfight.
那你还等什么 托雷托
You wait for it…
不！
No!
莱蒂 站住！
Letty, stop!
你打算怎么做？
What are you gonna do?
我不知道你为什么要这么做
I don't know why you're doing this,
但我清楚一件事 你是爱我的
but I know one thing. You love me.
而且你不会对我开枪的
And you're not gonna to shoot me.
你早该把箱子给他 省的我来追你了
You should've given him the case, cause I won't chase you.
那好吧
Okay.
我只能从死人手里抢了
I will just take it from a dead girl.
想把自己搭进去吗？
You willing to die for it?
我们回去吧
Let's go then.
怎么样了？
Anything?
他们跑了
They're gone.
国防部刚确认 那就是核密码箱
And D.O.D confirmed it was a nuclear football.
他拿着电磁脉冲武器以及核武器发射密码
He's got an EMP and nuclear launch codes.
不知道他们想干嘛
I don't know what it is,
但绝对有阴谋
but they're building towards something.
戴克呢？
Deckard?
他没挺过来
He didn't make it.
你令我很失望 多姆
I'm disappointed in you, Dom.
行动紧要关头 你竟然让莱蒂带着密码箱走了
You're gonna Letty just walk away with the codes.
- 你拿到密码了！- 是罗兹拿回的密码
- You've got the codes! - Rhodes got the codes.
而你选择了放她走
You made the choice to let her go.
现在我也要做出选择了
And now I have to make one on my own.
你看这些个小家伙多能招人疼啊 是吗？
They are adorable little things, aren't they?
天啊 我真不希望伤害他
I hope I don't hurt him.
听着神经病 我可是全按你说的办的
Look, Cipher, I did exactly what you asked me to do.
你不要这样
Don't do this.
- 这就是你的报应 - 是我的报应吗？
- This is your doing - My doing?
爸爸爸 爸爸 爸爸
Pa pa pa Pa pa Pa pa.
求你不要伤害他 我求你了
Please don't hurt him. I'm begging you.
我不需要你来求我
I don't want you to beg.
- 我要你从中吸取教训 - 吸取什么？
- I want you to learn - Learn what?
我明白你为什么会那么做 我真的很清楚
I understand why you did what you did. I really do.
但你的选择是错的
But it was the wrong choice.
而这就是你所带来的后果
This is a consequence, Dom.
不！不！不
No! No! No…
等等 等等
Wait Wait.
- 多姆 先救你儿子 - 不！不！
- Dom, save your son first - No! No!
能调取巷子里那男的监控吗
Can you pull up the footage from the guy in the ally.
- 找交通监控 - 明白了
- Traffic cams - I got you.
就知道是他 这个男的我认识他
I knew it. I recognize that guy.
他叫康纳·罗兹
That's Connor Rhodes.
我和肖的弟兄合作时见过他
I met him when I was working with Shaw's brother.
他要我们帮他偷龙葵
He wanted us to get the Nightshade device him.
康纳·罗兹
Connor Rhodes.
他和一个我很讨厌的人也有关联
He's also linked to somebody who I like to forget.
摩西·贾康德
Mose Jakande.
这个觊觎天眼的小军阀
Warlord who tried to get God's eye.
也就是说多姆有两次坏了塞弗的好事
Which means that's twice that Dom has messed up Cipher's business.
你现在感受到的一切
Everything you're feeling right now,
无论是愤怒还是悲痛 都不是真实的
that's rage, sense of loss. It's not real.
保证人类种族的延续
It's a survival instinct wired deep into our brains.
不过是深深扎根于我们大脑中的一种生态本能
To ensure continuation of species.
当初我们的先人去水边打水时
When early men went visit a watering hole…
要是有个一不留神 孩子被鳄鱼叼走
If they didn't watch their child, they got snatched by a crocodile.
我们的大脑 会生成充满着悲痛 但又有指令作用的记忆
Their brains would create a painful but a structural memory.
这样就能避免悲剧重演
So it will never happen again.
家庭这个观念是你思想的核心
This idea of family that is so core with you,
也主宰者你的世界
that rules your world…
但它只是个生物界的谎言
It's a biological lie.
你没必要相信他
You don't have to accept it.
我就不信！
I don't!
你真以为你毁掉我两支队伍
Did you really could think you could destroy two of my teams.
还不用承担后果吗？
Without any repercussions?
要不是因为这些破事
I wouldn't have even looked your way…
我本来看都不会看你一眼
If you hadn't done that.
你也不知道自己有个儿子
You didn't even know you had a kid.
你应该感谢我
You can thank me for that.
做我要求你做的
And start doing the job I'm asking you to do.
要我帮你挑起战争吗
Help you start a war.
你以为我要这个
Is that what you think I want.
思路太局限了啊
That's so limited.
我拿密码箱不是要开战
I didn't take that football to start a war…
扣下你儿子也不是要成家
Anymore than I took your son to start a family.
扣你儿子能帮我拿到密码
Taking your son got me the codes…
密码让我掌控核弹
The codes will get me the nukes,
核弹让我掌控我所要的…
and the nukes will get me what I want…
比如今天 比如明天 比如今后的每一天
Today, tomorrow… and every day after that.
你想要什么？
What's that?
至高无上的权限
Accountability.
等我引爆一两个核弹头
The second I fire off
one of those nukes…
这些个世界上的超级大国就都会明白
I put the superpowers of this world on notice that…
只要他们一越过底线
… when they cross the line,
我就会出马 拿他们一一问罪
… I'm gonna be there to hold the responsible…
多姆 这终极真相就是
Because the truth is, Dom…
对这个世界而言
… To the world out there…
我就是水面下那潜伏的鳄鱼
… I'm the crocodile at the watering hole.
该干这最后一票了
You've got one last job to do.
塞弗
Cipher…
那时我要是你 就会亲我儿子
If I were you, I would kiss my son.
因为无论你在乎与否 所有这一切
Because whether you value it or not, all of this…
你的飞机 你的安保力量还有你自己
Your plane, your security and you…
还能存在 全因为有他
… are still on this earth because of him.
我们之前无法追踪到塞弗
The problem we have with tracking Cipher.
是因为没有任何头绪
is there's nothing to trace then.
但现在我们有了罗兹的信息
Now we have Rhodes' information.
而且我们抢在他数据
And we're getting snapshots of this data.
被清除前保存了截图
before it's scrubbed off the net.
这看着像是个银行账户 为什么我们不直接黑进去？
That looks like somebody's bank accounts? Always just…
这表示的是经度
The Longitude.
鉴于多姆袭击的是俄罗斯车队
Given the fact that Dom hit the Russian Motorcade.
他差不多就在俄罗斯 调出地图来
safe to say it's Russia. Go ahead, bring up the map.
好 我们来一个个过一遍
Great, let's start here run the possibilities.
雅尔塔 波尔塔瓦
Yalta, Poltava.
看起来就是一大堆陌生名字
Looks like they just threw letters together.
- 科诺恩约特 - 是弗拉多夫
- Konyert - It's Vladupi.
你怎么来了？
What are you doing here?
干嘛 我说过会时不时
Thought I was gonna check in on you from time to time,
来看看你们进展
To see you how you're doing.
而且看起来 不怎么顺啊
By the way, not so hot.
但弗拉多夫寸草不生啊 就是个冰雪王国
But there's nothing in Vladiven. It's just ice…
有意思了
That funny…
我可以保证那有个俄罗斯秘密海军基地
Could've sworn there was a secret Russian naval base.
放置冷战时期潜水艇的
with the retrophilic cold war Submarines.
不过 严格意义上说 这基地已不属于俄方了
Well, technically, it's not Russian anymore.
它在一个月前被一伙搞分裂的恐怖份子占领了
Base was take by a terror grope of military separatists.
俄方到现在还没夺回来
about a month ago. And the Russians haven't taken it back yet.
所以我们行动有了个小窗口期
So there is a little window of opportunity here.
又是俄罗斯潜水艇 又是核密码箱
Russian submarines, nuclear football,
感觉我们不管怎么做都会被炸上天
it sounds like everything we do our legs gonna be bombed off.
感觉你还是名单上的第十一名呢
Sounds like you're still a No. 11 on the list.
我还感觉你嘴边长了毛
It sounds like you've changed since you look punk ass.
本该办事变得牢靠点
Facial hairs and camen.
各位 各位
Guys… guys. Hey.
这得向上汇报 双方一级级请示
We gotta call this in all the way up the chain.
想法没错啊 孩子
That's good thinking champ.
除了… 可是俄罗斯的防长
Except… unfortunately the Russian Minister of Defense.
在美国期间遭遇了一点小意外
Got himself involved in little incident on US territory.
双方磋商还需要一阵子
and two governments aren't talking to each other for a while.
等他们谈好我们也来不及了
By the time they do… It will be too late.
所以 你们还有别的建议吗？
So, any other suggestions?
我有个提议
Yeah, I got one.
要不我们自己动手吧？
How about we just stop them ourselves?
你说的可是俄罗斯的军事基地
You're talking about a Russian Military Base.
分裂分子的
Separatists.
是谁的不都是送死吗
Whatever. It's suicide.
我们要避免第三次世界大战
It's stopping world war 3.
你知道那后果吗？
What's it gonna be rook?
这回你要闭着眼等死吗？
You're gonna close your eyes on this one too?
祈祷世界末日
Pray that the apocalypse.
不会降临到自家门前
doesn't come knocking on your mama's front door?
或许你还不如扛起枪
Or are you're gonna saddle up,
站出来和我们一起拯救这乱七八糟的世界
be a man and save the entire goddamn world.
你知吗 我觉得我想明白了
You know, I think I figured it out.
明白什么啦？
What's that?
- 那第三条规矩 - 是什么呢？
- Rule number three - Which is?
天下压根就没规矩
There are no rules.
我说什么来着？
What did I told you, Luke?
我就知道他会想通的
I knew he'd get in three.
运输机一小时后起飞
Areal transport leaves in an hour.
要什么车随便挑 没任何限制
Take whatever vehicle you want. All bets are off.
- 没限制了 - 没任何限制？
- All bets are off - Bets are off?
那我们再会吧
See you later…
（俄罗斯 弗拉多夫）
莱蒂我本来不想告诉你的
Letty I don't like telling you this one thing,
计划现在有变化
The game's changed.
之前我们只是想抓住多姆
Before we were trying just to catch Dom,
但发生了这么多事儿
but now after all of this…
我要是迫不得已
I want you to know, if I have to…
还是要干掉他
I'm gonna put him down…
那你得连我一块儿杀了
Then you might have to take us both down.
这儿太差劲了 这里不适合我
I'm freezing man. This ain't for me.
我的生活方式跟这儿差别太大了
I come from a different kind of lifestyle brah.
姑娘们了解我 他们知道我什么样
Ladies know me. They know where I'm at with.
可我刚去解个手 都快认不出我自己了
I try to take a piss, I ain't even recognize myself.
哥们 你这信息量也太大了
Now that's entirely too much information.
我就是说说
I'm just saying.
对了 有件事可以确定
Well, one thing is for sure.
多姆他们不是互相配合 就是事先有交易
Dom's gotta be either working with them or making a train.
没人会蠢到不带军队来这种鬼地方
cause no one will be this insane to hit this place without a damn army.
这个我可说不准
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
一说他他就到
Speak of the Devil.
好了 多姆 你和大家庭团聚只有一步之遥了
Alright, Dom, you're one step closer to that family reunion.
距离基地400米
400 meters to base.
准备电磁脉冲炮 干掉对方防御网
Prep the EMP. Let's take these defenses down.
有潜在威胁靠近
We have a possible threat incoming.
立即升起路障 快 快
Raise the barricade, As soon as possible.
（EMP 备妥）
停电了 快进入防御
We've lost power, get to your positions now.
门打开了 好戏正式开演了
Gates are open. Let's get this party started.
（EMP 充电）
- 电磁脉冲在充电 - 要多久？
- EMP's are charging - How long?
需要六十秒
60 seconds.
好吧 多姆 你只剩一次脉冲可用了
Alright, Dom, You've one pulse left in that EMP.
那潜水艇基本是绝缘体
That sub is heavily insulated.
你到它正下方才有效果
You're gonna need to be right underneath it, for this thing to work.
拜托
Come on.
目标锁定 他在潜艇下面
Engaging target. He's beneath the Sub.
呼救 呼救 失去动力 我要坠毁了
I'm loosing control, mayday, mayday. I'm going down.
太棒了 这下子一箭双鵰了
Yes, two birds with one stone.
我们已控制了潜艇
We've got control of the sub.
多姆 我们进展顺利
Dom, we are good.
去会合吧 好的麦迪
Head over to the Rendezvous. Ok Matty…
让那小东西转起来吧
… Let's take this baby for a spin.
该死！
Damn!
塞弗刚重启了潜水艇指挥系统
I think Cipher just rebooted that Sub's command system.
他说什么鬼东西？
What the hell is he talking about?
用外行话说
In Leyman's terms…
她这是要劫走那艘潜艇
She just carjacked a submarine.
我们不能让它跑掉 那里是控制室
We can't let it get away. There's the control room.
如果你能把我带进那个仓库
If you can get me into that warehouse.
我就能入侵网络反向攻击塞弗
I can tap with network and counter hack Cipher.
阻止潜水艇下沉
Keep it from flowing into water.
不 现在只需要把我送上潜水艇
No, what we need to do is get me on that sub.
我去找武器室拔掉发射芯片
I find the weapon's room and I can pull the lunch chip.
阻止她发射核弹
before she can fire any of those nukes.
你这主意太疯狂了
That is too crazy.
- 你的主意又太危险 - 我们双管齐下
- Just saying it's too dangerous - We'll do both.
开门 开门！
Knock, knock!
五辆车刚刚到达了基地
Five vehicles just reached the base.
他们还真是锲而不舍啊
They just don't give up, do they…
好的 快点啊 各位 都快点 都快点
A'right. Let's haul ass team. Double time, double time.
打他们
Letty, let's roll.
快走 快走
Go, go, go, go.
计划有变 多姆
Change of plans, Dom.
我发现你一个新坐标 你立即给我赶过去
I'm sending you the co-ordinates, head there immediately.
- 我不干了 我要我儿子 - 你干不干得我说的算
- I'm done. I want my son - I'll tell you when you're done.
你的团队全来了 你必须和罗兹会合听我的指令
Your team is in play, now meet Rhodes and follow my instruction.
我掩护你 上
I got you covered, go.
出去 出去！快离开这 快 快 快！
Move, move! Get out of here, go go!
好的 你是不是喜欢这个？
Ok, how do you like this?
- 远程连接被切断了 - 这个我来处理吧
- Remote link has been separated - I'll take care of this.
你好啊 拉姆齐
Hi Ramsey.
她夺回控制了
She's regaining control.
该死的 她太厉害
Damn it, she's good.
他们进武器室了
They are entering the Weapon's room.
真可爱啊
Oh that's cute.
你拉啊 拉啊！罗曼 罗曼 赶快找到芯片 走
Go, pull pull! Roman, guard up by the chip, go.
她真狡猾 那我还得再放点大招
Oh she's slick. Gonna have to do better in that way.
好吧 你真要惹毛我了
Ok, now you're starting to piss me off.
拉姆齐 我们还需要多长时间？
Ramsey, how much time we talking to you?
你真聪明 但修行还是不够啊
You're smart, but no smart enough.
她把我封锁了
She's locked me out.
特尔佳 我阻止不了她 你一定要拔掉芯片
Tez, I can't stop. Now you're gonna have to pull that chip.
我也不行 这东西启动了攻击模式
I can't. This thing's going into attack mode.
芯片拔出来才能打开门
The door's not gonna open until you pull the chip.
特尔佳 应该拔那个 我们也不知道啊
Tez we got no idea what the hell we are looking for.
我找到了
I got it.
你们刚才到底干了什么啊？
What in the hell are you guys doing?
不是我 不是我干的好吧
It wasn't me, okay?
应该有标签 写着发射指令
It will be labeled "Guidance Go"
- 「发射指令」 - 好的 我好像有发现了
- "Guidance Go" - OK. I got something.
- 什么？- 上面写着 哈克弗拉 弗拉瓦赫…
- What? - It says haha… slack slack back.
斯摩 得赫瓦赫
… smoke, dear jack na jack.
你知道啥意思吗？
Do you understand that?
好吧 真难看
Well, nasty.
真是台好戏
Quite a show.
准备发射核弹
Arming the nuke.
核弹准备中 她正在开始发射了
Nuke's going hot, she's trying to fire this thing.
- 收到 我们马上出去 - 赶快令核弹失效
- Roger that, we're moving out - Disable the nukes.
罗曼 看到什么了？
Roman, what are you seeing?
- 快点 告诉我 - 狗屁都没看到 我还在看呢
- Come on, Talk to me - I don't see shit. I'm holding on.
我们开始倒计时
Now we have a countdown.
这到底怎么回事 伙计？
What the hell is going on man?
核弹马上要发射了 就是这么回事
We are about to launch a nuclear missile, what the hell is going on.
拔掉那该死的芯片
Pull the damn chip.
倒计时 倒计时 快找到倒计时
Countdown. Countdown. Look for a countdown.
什么倒计时？
What countdown?
核弹需要激活才能发射
The missile needs to activate for launch.
倒定时器肯定不是写俄文的
The countdown timer won't be in Russian.
倒计时
The countdown.
给这个世界一点颜色瞧瞧
Let's show the world what we've got.
不 不 不 不要按哪制
No. No. No. Don't press that.
我找到了
I got it.
出问题 发射不了
Something is wrong. It won't launch.
让潜水艇赶紧下水
Get that sub out of there.
现在！
Now!
快点啊 罗曼
Move your ass Roman.
你没事吧？
You alright?
这里一切都不听使唤了 快跑吧
There's nothing alright about any of this. Let's go.
那核弹怎么办？
What about the missiles?
拿到了芯片 她发射不了
We got the chip, no nukes for her.
太好了 我们走
Hell yeah. Let's roll.
伙计们 有追兵 一大批追兵
Guys we got company. A lot of company.
大家听好 计划是这样的
Alright team, here is the plan.
在海湾入口处有一个闸口
There is a Sea lock at the opening of the bay,
要能提前到达并关上
We get there first, and close it,
就能阻止潜艇进入开阔海域
we can stop the submarine from escaping into open water.
不然它就溜了
And disappearing forever.
位置已经确认 西南方向十英里处
I've got the location. It's 10 miles south west.
十英里？十秒钟我们到不了啊
10 miles? Like I make it in 10 seconds.
不不不不 这下不好了
No no no no, this is not good.
怎么了 罗曼 没装雪地胎吗？
What's the matter Roman, you forgot the snow tyre?
兰博基尼开的爽吗？
Loving that Lambo now?
好吧 各位 待会再处理芯片的事
Alright everyone, hold you with that launch trip later.
现在我要潜艇下潜到深海
Right now I want that sub in deep water,
避开所有探测
where no one can find it.
给我最快离开海湾的路线
Find me the fastest route out of that bay.
收到
Copy that.
他们干嘛都打我啊？
Why are they shooting at me?
谁叫你开桔黄色的兰博基尼啊
I think off you're in that orange Lamborghini I don't know.
给我闭嘴 特尔佳
Shut up Tez.
多姆
Dom.
你真的想发动那辆车吗？
Do you really wanna put that car in gear?
你想是吗？
Do you?
我可不这样认为
I don't think so.
他们正在赶往海闸那里
They're heading for the sea lock.
企图把我们潜艇困在海湾里
They're trying to trap the sub in the bay.
我很早之前就该做个了结
I should have taken care of this a long time ago.
罗兹 干掉他的团队
Rhodes, took his team out.
交给我吧
I'm on it.
罗曼 到我前面去
Roman, get in front of me.
好吧 你们来硬的是吧？
Ok, y'all wanna play it rough?
现在该轮到我了
Now it's my turn.
好样的 宝贝儿！
Yeah, baby!
各位 我们右侧有雪地摩托
Guys, we got snow mobile on the right.
他们要从两面夹击
They're going to flank us.
不 他们没机会！
No they ain't!
该死！
Oh shit!
特尔佳！
Tez!
罗曼 坚持住 我马上就到
Roman hold tight. I'm on the way.
我可不想下去游泳 不要！
I don't wanna go swimming. No!
不是吧？特尔佳
Really Tez?
噢 不不不不不…
Oh, No. No. No No…
该死
Oh shit.
罗曼 抓紧车门
Roman, grab your door.
特尔佳！
Tez!
抓住车门 罗曼
Grab the door Roman.
这下完了 天啊
It's all gone. Oh Shit.
这是什么回事呀！
What is going on.
罗曼 坚持住
Roman, hang on.
特尔佳！
Tej!
快让我下来
Get me off this thing.
特尔佳
Tez.
快啊！
Come on!
好吧 这烂摊子我真是受够了！
Alright, I've had enough of this shit!
谁说我是第十一名
Number 11 my Ass.
别害怕 我们还要拦截潜艇呢 上来
Don't shrink it. We got a sub to catch, get in.
又怎么了？
What?
货舱发出了降压警告
The pressure is on alert in the cargo hold.
降到一万英尺
Drop it to 10 thousand feet.
我知道这些人对你来说有多重要
I know how much these people mean to you.
所以我让你选第一个目标
So I'll let you pick the first target.
我不会隔着一英里挑目标
I'm not picking target from a mile away.
我会和他们面对面站着 看着对方眼睛
I'd stand face to face, and look 'em dead in the eye.
那好吧
Ok.
就挑你老婆吧
The wife it is.
（等待连接）
飞机不错啊 我愿意接手它
Nice plane. I'm gonna enjoy her remains.
别瞎打主意了
You don't go get any ideas.
你吃飞机的亏还少吗
You and planes don't have a good history.
不是吧
No shit.
走吧 小子 这些混蛋可不会自己来送死
Let's go scarface. The arseholes ain't gonna kill themselves.
现在就调出监控画面
Pull up surveillance, right now.
惊喜不
Surprise.
你不是已经死了吗
Pierce must be dead.
你来开车 我一开始就说了
You're driving. I said it from the beginning.
不可以 我不开车
No way, I'm not driving.
货舱部位出现入侵的情况 立即给我处理
We have a security breach in the cargo hold. Take care of it now.
天呀 老妈 你应避开神经来打啊
Jesus Mum, you should pose to avoid the nerves.
闭嘴吧 别这么孩子气
Oh, shut up, don't be such a baby.
去找飞行员 他有第二把钥匙
Get to the pilot, he's got the second key.
然后等我信号
Wait for my signal.
代我向塞弗问好
Give Cipher my regards.
托雷托他履行承诺了吗？
Did Torretto hold up his end of the deal?
他给我们留下了这个小东西
He gave us this little thing here.
不不不 别碰
No, don't touch.
你可以用这个追踪到塞弗
You can track Cipher with this,
但你不能一个人去 必须得两个人
but you can't do this on your own. There's gotta be two of you.
好吧 我这儿有熟人
Fine, I got contacts.
不 你带你弟弟去
Now you're gonna take your brother.
- 别啊 - 听话
- No - Yes.
托雷托知道他在哪
Torretto knows where he is…
他用这东西就能看到一切 好像叫恶魔的屁眼之类？
He's got this thing. He can see everything it's like it's called the devil's bumhole or something?
- 它叫天眼 - 好吧 随便吧
- It's called the God's eyes - Yeah, well. Whatever.
我不可能带上欧文 好吧？
There's no way I'm using Owen, alright?
他无药可救了
He's a lost cause.
他可是你兄弟 戴克
He's your brother, Deck.
他还是我儿子呢 是我们的家人
He's my son. He's our family.
我们的家人
And our family that died…
怎么可以死在监狱里
Bloody shit happening.
你怎么能这么说欧文 老娘真不敢相信
You lied about, I mean, I can't believe you.
你真气死我了 你真让妈好难过
You've gotten upset, you really upset your mother.
你还配当哥哥吗你 你这个…
Call yourself a brother?
别这样 妈妈 好吧 好吧
Look, I'm in, mum. Ok.
每次都这样！
Every time!
- 欧文 - 就位了
- Owen - In position.
开始
Go.
我进来了
I'm in.
（等待连接）
（来电 私人号码）
包裹已经到手了 托雷托
I've got the package to lay on.
毫发无损啊
Whole pounds of him…
爸 爸 爸 爸 爸
Pa pa pa pa pa.
你弄得我打偏了目标
You made me miss my son.
你在搞什么鬼？
What do you think you're doing?
盯着你至死为止
Looking at you dead in the eye.
这个是为了埃琳娜
That was for Letty.
- 罗兹 - 他永不能陪着我们了
- Rhodes - He is no longer with us.
罗兹选错了目标
Rhodes picked the wrong target.
恭喜你啊 多姆
Congratulations Dom.
你刚害死你亲儿子
You just killed your son.
你错了
You are wrong.
他刚被我救了
I just saved him.
而你刚好放虎归山
And you just took your foot off the tiger's neck.
好了 待会可能有点吵
You're welcome. It's gonna get noisy.
这是给你准备的
This is for your relief.
好听吗？
Good?
我们走
Let's go.
不 给我拦住他 不许让他下飞机
Go stop him, do not let him get off this plane.
又有个大麻烦 那卡车的导弹够干掉我们所有人
That truck's got enough munition to take us all out.
那就别被它瞄准
We don't give 'em a target.
都开到前面
Everybody get in front of us,
排成一列准备攻击
line up, we will take the hit.
什么？我现在就要换车
What? I need to switch cars, right now.
瞄准锁定
- 罗曼 现在要受点苦头了 - 什么？
- Roman, here comes the bad part - What?
大家坚持住！我们就快到海闸了
Hang in there guys! We're almost through the lock.
你说得轻巧 又不是你屁股着了火
It's easy for you to say, when your ass ain't on fire.
好了 小家伙
Alright little mate.
下面可能有点吓人
It's might be a little scary,
但也会很有趣
It's gonna be a lot of fun.
音乐好听吗？
Has the music good?
他们锁定目标了
They're locking on.
抱歉各位 我也没招了
Sorry guys, I got no trick for us…
- 现在怎么办啊？- 大家都祈祷吧
- What do we do now? - We start praying.
太牛了！
Hell yeah!
是多姆！
That's Dom!
他又跟我们一伙儿了
This guy in our side now.
管他呢 反正他刚才救了我们
Who the hell cares, He just saved our asses.
真高兴 又能和你一起飚车了
Good to be riding with you again man.
托雷托为他们开了路
Torretto just cleared the way for them.
谁来给我点回应啊
Someone give me something.
- 鱼雷准备完毕 - 那就发射啊
- Torpedoes are ready - Then launch them.
该死
Shit.
- 你来把方向盘 - 我就不做
- Take the wheel - I ain't taking shit.
你来把方向盘
Take the wheel!
你要去哪？
Where are you doing?
- 你真是疯了！- 加速啊
- This is crazy! - Speed up,
- 往左打死！- 什么？
- Left and back! - What?
你把方向盘向左快速打死不就完事了吗
Turn the goddamn wheel to the left, really quickly.
喔 宝贝儿！
Boom, baby!
我们走一个！
That's alright!
马上回来
Back in the sink.
来笑一个？
Where is that smile?
真乖！
There it is!
你居然朝婴儿开枪 你混蛋到家了你
You're gonna shoot a baby You shoud bust it…
这个你还是别看了？
You aren't gonna wanna see this?
这味儿是你的还是他的？
Is that you or him?
是他的 好
Him. Good.
鱼雷没击中目标
The torpedo's missed,
他们会在我们之前抵达海闸
they are gonna reach lock before the sub does.
他们休想
The hell they are.
等着看好戏吧
Get ready for this.
坏了！
Oh shit!
我们得换辆大点的车
We're going to need a bigger truck.
就在我们正下方 快离开这儿
They are right down of us, get out the way.
- 快离开这儿 - 你怎么就知道大喊大叫
- Get us out of here - Why are you always yelling?
- 那贱人疯了吗？- 小心！
- This bitch is crazy! - Look out!
这可不太妙
That's not good.
非常不妙
拜托告诉我 我们不需要太担心
Please tell me there's nothing we need to worry about.
没问题的
We got this.
不愧是我的女人
That's my girl.
潜水艇距离太近
The sub's too close.
我们来不及赶到闸口了
We ain't making it to the gate in time.
就这么让它走了吗？
We just gonna let it get away?
有多姆在 就不会
Not if I know Dom.
你输定了 多姆
You loose. Dom.
我灭了你两支队伍
I destroyed two of your teams.
还杀了你的红头发男友
I killed your red headed boyfriend.
还把两枚炸弹放到你那可躲避追踪的飞机上
And I put two killers on your untraceable plane.
你打扰我度蜜月那一刻起就已经输了
You lost the minute you interrupted my honeymoon.
现在猜猜我为谁而来
Now guess whom I'm coming for.
热追踪导弹瞄准他
Put a heat-seeker on him now.
快！
Now!
发射！
Fire!
那可是个热追踪导弹
That's a goddamn heat seeker coming at us.
分头跑 往海边跑
Peel off, head to the shore.
好吧 赶紧来吧
Oh my… come and get it.
不 不 不要！
No no… No!
各位！快下潜
Guys! Dive…
这个是替我儿子报仇！
This… This is for my son!
多姆！
Dom!
你没子弹了 戴克
You are out of bullets Deckard.
我收拾你根本不需要用枪
Like I'm need a gun to take care of you,
你怎么找到我的？
How did you find me?
你想看看以前的多姆吗 看好了！
You want to see the old Dom? Watch!
真是机智啊
Resourceful.
你要为很多事情负责啊
You have a lot to answer Cipher.
你让我们家受了多大罪
You pulled my family through.
气的我妈
A mother.
我要确保历史在任何人身上
I'm gonna make sure that never happens again.
都不再重演
To anyone.
而你的计划只有一个漏洞
There is only one flaw in your plan.
什么漏洞？
What's that?
我俩就我拿着降落伞！
Only one of us has a parachute!
我说了 会很好玩儿的！
Told you this would be fun!
该降落了 伙计们！
Time to land, Boys!
你知道我永远不会丢下你的？
You know I've never left you, Letty?
我知道
I know.
你知道我以后也不会的
And you know I never will…
我也知道
I know.
我有好多话想跟你说
I've so much to tell you.
可不是吗 你可以从那个贱人开始说！
Yeah you do, and you can start with that bitch!
他还是他 多姆尼克·托雷托
Now, that's… Dominic Toretto.
多姆！我不想打断你们
Hey Dom! I'm just towing it out there?
但我们得离开这
We need to get up out of here.
因为冰下都是核武器之类的玩意
Cause this all kinda neuclearism happening under this ice.
放心吧 没有触发芯片这些核弹没有危险
Relax! Without the trigger chips, those nukes are harmless.
好吧 那我们没事了
Ok. So we good then.
我要来点高难度的自拍
Lemme go and get my young selfie levels up.
你知道这是涉密的吧
You realize this is classified, right?
今天不是
Not today.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
好了 赶紧将身躯带离这里 我快冻死了
Alright, can we give our body out of here now. I'm freezing.
都没事啦
It's Okay.
别担心 他很快就会到
Don't worry, he's gonna be here soon.
我知道 他们有很多共同爱好
I get it, y'all got a lot in common.
计算机黑客 天眼系统 技术狂 书呆子
Computer hacks, god's eyes, geeks, nerd.
但我俩也有很多共同点 是吧？
You know, but we got a lot in common too! Alright?
- 比如说呢？- 我俩不论走到哪
- Like what? - We walk in the room,
都能瞬间吸引异性的目光
and we are oozing sex appeal.
我俩光站在一起就要出问题
Me and you? There's a problem.
我要问个严肃的问题了
I am asking the real question right now.
两部电影给你选
Is it gonna be…
是《菜鸟大反攻》呢 还是《黑暗骑士》呢？
"The Revenge of Nerds?" or "The Dark Knight?"
坦白说 你俩我都喜欢
To be honest I like both of you.
- 这就对了 - 我怎样给你说 宝贝
- A'rigt! Yeah…yea! - What I told you! Babay.
但在我们聊这个之前
But just before we get into all of that,
让我问你们一个问题
Let me ask you one question.
- 你想问我什么都行 - 什么都行
- You can ask me anything - Anything.
知道我姓什么吗？
What's my last name?
等你们搞清楚了 然后再向我汇报吧
When you guys figured it out, then I guess you can let me know.
反正以后姓帕克 这个才是重要的 是吧
It's gonna be a Parker. That's all that really matters.
是琼斯吗 叫帕克夫人
Jones, Miss Parker.
帕克夫人
Hey Miss Parker.
- 嘻 - 莱蒂
- Hey - Letty.
真的要谢谢你
I wanted to thank you.
不用客气
No need.
塞弗还在逃
Cipher's still on the loose.
有线报称她在雅典
There's been some reports she's in Athens.
但她近期是不会对任何城市发动核袭
But she won't be nuking any city anytime soon.
感谢你们大家了
Thanks to you guys.
- 对了 我给你们带了份礼物来 - 肯定不是好东西
- So, I got you a parting favor - This can't be good…
你的记录抹掉了 官复原职 你又可以上岗了
Your record's been cleared. Full re-instatement. You got you job back.
当然 得你本人愿意
That is if you want it.
要我愿意？
If I want?
我都干了16年了
You know after 16 years.
也该歇一阵子了
I figured it's time for a little break.
哇哦
Wow.
我要当全职爸爸咯
Daddy's stayin' home.
- 无名氏 - 保持联系！
- Nobody - Get in touch!
等等
Ah, hang on a second.
这下有意思了
This could be interesting.
你怎么知道我会配合？
What made you think I would do it?
因为手足情 看到你对塞弗的表情
Brother-hood. I saw that look you gave Cipher.
就知道你想报仇
I knew you wanted revenge.
很高兴 我猜对了
Glad I did it.
没想到 你敢去找我妈
Can't believe you went to see my Mother.
瞧你闹的大动静
All this fuss of you.
就是
Yes.
埃琳娜 我保证我儿子会平安的
Elena, I promise to keep our son safe.
会永远平安下去的
And now… he always will be.
我现在想把你介绍给我
I want to introduce you to the most.
全宇宙最重要的人
important person in my universe.
她从来没有放弃过我
Who will never give up on me.
他长得多美
He's beatiful.
我曾经说过 人永远不可以背叛家人
You've heard me say."That you never turn your back on family"
而我想感谢大家 从来没有放弃过我
And I wanna thank you all for never turning your back on me.
认识一下大家吧
You wanna meet them.
好吧！
Alright!
介绍一下
Everyone…
布莱恩·托雷托
Meet Bryan.
布莱恩
Hey Bryan.
欢迎加入家庭 布莱恩
Welcome to your family, Bryan.
好 该轮到我做餐前祈祷了
Okay, I guess he's my turning to say christ.
我们感谢您赐予我们家人
Thank you for giving us family.
我们坐在这儿祈祷
We sit here, Christ.
感谢您给予我们力量
Thank you for giving us the strength.